Africana Center Records UA113
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, circa 1939 -- 2011; UA113.004; 6.64 Linear Feet; 4 Digital Object(s) 4 digital objects containing 28 files.; 1.086 Megabytes
  - Awards banquet, 1980; UA113.004.005.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 40, Box 5)
  - Awards dinner, 1981 -- 1987; UA113.004.005.00032; 4 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 41-44, Box 5)
  - Awards dinner nominations, 1986; UA113.004.005.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 45, Box 5)
  - Bell, Jewell H., 1988 -- 1990; UA113.004.005.00034; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 46-47, Box 5)
  - Between Sisters conference, 1998; UA113.004.005.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 48, Box 5)
  - Biology 14 - Francie Chew, circa 1994 -- 1995; UA113.004.005.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 49, Box 5)
  - Black Alumni Association records, 1976 -- 2000; UA113.004.001; 24 Folder(s)
    This file contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
    - Alumnae/Homecoming invitation, 1999; UA113.004.006.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 1, Box 6)
    - Alumni mailing, circa 1977 -- 183; UA113.004.006.00002; 3 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 2-4, Box 6)
    - Alumni mailing list (regional), circa 1983; UA113.004.006.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 5, Box 6)
    - Black Alumni Association records, circa 1977 -- 1994; UA113.004.006.00004; 3 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 6-8, Box 6)
    - Black Alumni Association questionnaires, circa 1981; UA113.004.006.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 9, Box 6)
    - Black alumni correspondence, circa 1977 -- 1987; UA113.004.006.00006; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 10-11, Box 6)
    - Black alumni information, circa 1985; UA113.004.006.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 12, Box 6)
    - Black alumni homecoming weekend, 2000; UA113.004.006.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 13, Box 6)
    - Black alumni project, circa 1987 -- 1992; UA113.004.006.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 14, Box 6)
    - Black alumni reunion, circa 1986 -- 1992; UA113.004.006.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 15, Box 6)
    - Black alumni weekend, circa 1976 -- 1978; UA113.004.006.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 16, Box 6)
    - List of black alumni, circa 1980; UA113.004.006.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 17, Box 6)
    - Tufts Black Alumni Association, 1994; UA113.004.006.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 18, Box 6)
    - Tufts Black Alumni Association membership, circa 1991 -- 1992; UA113.004.006.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 19, Box 6)
    - Tufts Black Alumni Association membership forms, circa 1991 -- 1992; UA113.004.006.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 20, Box 6)
    - Tufts Black Alumni Association membership lists and forms, circa 1991 -- 1992; UA113.004.006.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 21, Box 6)
    - Tufts Black Alumni Association, circa 1980 -- 1995; UA113.004.006.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 22, Box 6)
    - Tufts University Black Alumni Survey, circa 1995; UA113.004.006.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 23, Box 6)
    - Reunion '94 correspondence and photographs, 1994; UA113.004.006.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 24, Box 6)
  - Black Awards Banquet, circa 1980 -- 1990; UA113.004.006.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 25, Box 6)
  - Black Caucus records, 1981 -- 1989; UA113.004.006.00021; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 26-27, Box 6)
  - Black Caucus correspondence, 1976 -- 188; UA113.004.006.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 28, Box 6)
  - Blackburn Loan Fund, 1993 -- 1994; UA113.004.006.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 29, Box 6)
  - Black faculty dinners, 1993 -- 1996; UA113.004.006.00024; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 30-31, Box 6)
  - Black faculty/staff, circa 1994 -- 2000; UA113.004.006.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 32, Box 6)
  - Black Greeks at Tufts, 1987; UA113.004.006.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 33, Box 6)
  - Black history, 1999; UA113.004.006.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 34, Box 6)
  - Black History Month, 1981 -- 1983; UA113.004.006.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 35, Box 6)
  - Black History Month, 1987; UA113.004.006.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 36, Box 6)
  - Black History Month 1989, 1987 -- 1989; UA113.004.006.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 37, Box 6)
  - Black History Month '95, 1993 -- 1995; UA113.004.006.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 38, Box 6)
  - Black History Month '97, circa 1995 -- 1997; UA113.004.006.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 39, Box 6)
  - Black History Month 1998, 1996 -- 1998; UA113.004.006.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 40, Box 6)
  - Black History Month, 1999; UA113.004.006.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 41, Box 6)
  - Black History Month, circa 2003; UA113.004.006.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 42, Box 6)
  - Black History Month and Women's History Month event calendars, 2003; UA113.004.006.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 43, Box 6)
  - Black History Month events and programs, circa 1995 -- 1996; UA113.004.006.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 44, Box 6)
  - Black History Month event fliers, 1987; UA113.004.006.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 45, Box 6)
  - Black History Month events memo, 1980; UA113.004.006.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 46, Box 6)
  - Black History Month resources, 1996 -- 1998; UA113.004.006.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 47, Box 6)
  - Black parents weekend and award banquet, 1979 -- 1980; UA113.004.006.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 48, Box 6)
  - Black Student Awards nomination forms, 1988; UA113.004.006.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 49, Box 6)
  - Black Studies in Higher Education, 1980; UA113.004.006.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 50, Box 6)
  - Black women's group 1993-94, circa 1992 -- 1994; UA113.004.006.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 51, Box 6)
  - Black women's group flier, circa 1999; UA113.004.006.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 52, Box 6)
  - Black writers, circa 1996 -- 1997; UA113.004.006.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 53, Box 6)
  - Blaxploitation, circa 2000 -- 2001; UA113.004.007.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 1, Box 7)
  - Bogan and Armstrong concert, 1983; UA113.004.007.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 2, Box 7)
  - Bobo, Lawrence meeting, 2000; UA113.004.007.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 3, Box 7)
  - Bond, Julian poster/flier, 1986; UA113.004.007.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 4, Box 7)
  - Book catalogs, 1984; UA113.004.007.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 5, Box 7)
  - Boston Pan-African Forum, circa 2000; UA113.004.007.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 6, Box 7)
  - Brochure, circa 1980 -- 2000; UA113.004.007.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 7, Box 7)
  - Bullins, Ed, 1995; UA113.004.007.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 8, Box 7)
  - Byrd, Donald, 2000; UA113.004.007.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 9, Box 7)
  - Busting Out coordinators, 1991; UA113.004.007.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 10, Box 7)
  - Calendars and events, 2003 -- 2004; UA113.004.007.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 11, Box 7)
  - Calendar announcement, 1985; UA113.004.007.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 12, Box 7)
  - Cantave, Sophia, circa 1997 -- 2003; UA113.004.007.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 13, Box 7)
  - Capen House records, 1988 -- 1999; UA113.004.002; 14 Folder(s)
    - The African American Center and Capen House, circa 1996; UA113.004.007.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 14, Box 7)
    - Capen House and programing, 1993 -- 1999; UA113.004.007.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 15, Box 7)
    - Capen House applications, circa 1988; UA113.004.007.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 16, Box 7)
    - Capen House applications, 1989 -- 1990; UA113.004.007.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 17, Box 7)
    - Capen House applications for residency, 1990 -- 1991; UA113.004.007.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 18, Box 7)
    - Capen House applications, 1991 -- 1992; UA113.004.007.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 19, Box 7)
    - Capen House assignments, 1988 -- 1991; UA113.004.007.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 20, Box 7)
    - Capen House assignments '92 - '93, circa 1991 -- 1993; UA113.004.007.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 21, Box 7)
    - Capen House and Cape Cod resources, 1997 -- 1998; UA113.004.007.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 22, Box 7)
    - Capen House residents and peer advisors, 1998 -- 1999; UA113.004.007.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 23, Box 7)
    - Housing applications, circa 1993 -- 1994; UA113.004.007.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 24, Box 7)
    - Housing applications '94-'95, circa 1993 -- 1995; UA113.004.012.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 1, Box 12)
    - Housing assignments, 1994; UA113.004.007.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 25, Box 7)
    - Housing contract, circa 1993 -- 1995; UA113.004.007.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 26, Box 7)
    - Housing folder Capen House (African-Amer), circa 1994; UA113.004.007.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 27, Box 7)
  - Career guides and other sites of interest, web resources, 1998; UA113.004.007.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 28, Box 7)
  - Carpenter, Willie Ivory, circa 1991 -- 1999; UA113.004.007.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 29, Box 7)
  - Certificates of appreciation from the Caribbean Club, 1998 -- 1999; UA113.004.007.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 30, Box 7)
  - Chart-3 self assessment sheet, circa 1980; UA113.004.007.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 31, Box 7)
  - Clippings, circa 1939 -- 2011; UA113.004.007.00032; 7 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 32-38, Box 7)
  - Cole, Elizabeth R. research proposal approval, 1997; UA113.004.007.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 39, Box 7)
  - Collins, Patricia Hill correspondence and memos, circa 1978 -- 1979; UA113.004.007.00034; 3 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 40-42, Box 7)
  - Community resource guide, circa 1997 -- 1999; UA113.004.007.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 43, Box 7)
  - Community service awards, 1994; UA113.004.007.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 44, Box 7)
  - Community service awards, 1999; UA113.004.007.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 45, Box 7)
  - Conference bureau, 1993; UA113.004.007.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 46, Box 7)
  - Conference bureau workshop on prejudice - 8/5, 1986; UA113.004.007.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 47, Box 7)
  - Conference on Blacks in Higher Education, circa 1981 -- 1987; UA113.004.007.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 48, Box 7)
  - Conference Study of Presidency, 1987; UA113.004.007.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 49, Box 7)
  - Commencement open house, 1994; UA113.004.007.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 50, Box 7)
  - Course listings and correspondence, circa 1996 -- 2001; UA113.004.007.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 51, Box 7)
  - Craigville Conference, 1992 -- 1997; UA113.004.007.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 52, Box 7)
  - C.R.I.M.P., circa 1985 -- 1986; UA113.004.007.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 53, Box 7)
  - Current concerns, circa 1986; UA113.004.007.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 54, Box 7)
  - Cultural Expo week-end, 1980; UA113.004.007.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 55, Box 7)
  - Culture houses, circa 1952 -- 1978; UA113.004.007.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 56, Box 7)
  - Davis, Angela Y., 2000; UA113.004.007.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 57, Box 7)
  - Dean's list, 1977; UA113.004.007.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 58, Box 7)
  - Desert Night Training, 1997; UA113.004.008.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 1, Box 8)
  - Diversity meetings, 1986; UA113.004.008.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 2, Box 8)
  - Diversity Panel Co 94-95, 1994; UA113.004.008.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 3, Box 8)
  - The Donald Byrd Dance Foundation, Inc., circa 1994; UA113.004.008.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 4, Box 8)
  - Employment materials; personnel, 1991; UA113.004.008.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 5, Box 8)
  - Equal education opportunity committee, circa 1977 -- 1980; UA113.004.008.00006; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 6-7, Box 8)
  - Equipment transfer program forms, 1993; UA113.004.008.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 8, Box 8)
  - Events, 2001 -- 2003; UA113.004.008.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 9, Box 8)
  - Event space requests, circa 1998 -- 1999; UA113.004.008.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 10, Box 8)
  - Expo weekend folder, 1980; UA113.004.008.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 11, Box 8)
  - Expo weekend letters, 1980; UA113.004.008.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 12, Box 8)
  - Eyes on the Prize, 1987; UA113.004.008.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 13, Box 8)
  - Film rental, circa 1981 -- 1991; UA113.004.008.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 14, Box 8)
  - Fiscal, 1992 -- 1993; UA113.004.008.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 15, Box 8)
  - Fiscal year 1999 budget, 1998; UA113.004.008.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 16, Box 8)
  - Forms racial documentation, 1987; UA113.004.008.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 17, Box 8)
  - Freshmen lists, circa 1992 -- 1998; UA113.004.008.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 18, Box 8)
  - Goodman, Mark D. memos and correspondence, circa 1994 -- 1995; UA113.004.008.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 19, Box 8)
  - Greater Boston Inter-University Council, 1985 -- 1989; UA113.004.008.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 20, Box 8)
  - GTE Focus Grant, 1986; UA113.004.008.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 21, Box 8)
  - Guidelines for determination of academic standing, 1998; UA113.004.008.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 23, Box 8)
  - Handbook '93 - '94, circa 1993 -- 1994; UA113.004.008.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 24, Box 8)
  - Harlem Exchange, circa 1993; UA113.004.008.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 25, Box 8)
  - Health services, 1977 -- 1980; UA113.004.008.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 26, Box 8)
  - Holman United Methodist Church, circa 1996; UA113.004.008.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 27, Box 8)
  - Hooks, Bell, 1999 -- 2000; UA113.004.008.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 28, Box 8)
  - Howard, Anita, circa 1990 -- 1995; UA113.004.008.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 29, Box 8)
  - Hunter, Gregory 1970 - 1995, UA113.004.008.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 30, Box 8)
  - Instructor's Manual to Accompany Studies in Drama, Form B, 1964; UA113.004.008.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 31, Box 8)
  - International Worldtech, 1986; UA113.004.008.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 32, Box 8)
  - Johns, Karen Y., circa 1983 -- 1992; UA113.004.008.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 33, Box 8)
  - Johns, Karen Y. travel, 1991; UA113.004.008.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 34, Box 8)
  - Joint peer leader training facilitator guide, 2000; UA113.004.008.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 35, Box 8)
  - Joint peer leader training facilitator guide, 2002; UA113.004.008.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 36, Box 8)
  - Lectures/workshops, circa 1993 -- 1994; UA113.004.008.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 37, Box 8)
  - Malveaux, Julianne, 1996; UA113.004.008.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 38, Box 8)
  - Marable, Manning, circa 1984 -- 1985; UA113.004.008.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 39, Box 8)
  - McFadden, Todd S. correspondence, clippings, and fliers, 1994 -- 1995; UA113.004.008.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 40, Box 8)
  - McFadden, Todd S. travel, 1996 -- 1997; UA113.004.008.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 41, Box 8)
  - Meetings, circa 1981 -- 1987; UA113.004.008.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 42, Box 8)
  - Minority recruitment, 1985; UA113.004.008.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 43, Box 8)
  - MLK celebration, 2002; UA113.004.008.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 44, Box 8)
  - Moore, David D, circa 1978 -- 1996; UA113.004.008.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 45, Box 8)
  - Multicultural AIDS Coalition, Inc., circa 1996 -- 1997; UA113.004.008.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 46, Box 8)
  - Museum of Afro American History African Meeting House membership certificate, 1990; UA113.004.008.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 47, Box 8)
  - New England Consortium of Black Admissions Counselors, five year report, 1976-1981, UA113.004.008.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 48, Box 8)
  - Office of Equal Opportunity Affirmative Action pamphlet, circa 1995 -- 2005; UA113.004.008.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 49, Box 8)
  - Office files, 1971 -- 1980; UA113.004.008.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 50, Box 8)
  - Office files, circa 1978 -- 1990; UA113.004.008.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 51, Box 8)